Resume

Name: Mou-Chun Wang

• Email: mjwangtw@gmail.com

· Phone: 0930082698

Summary

• Over 5 Years backend development experience (PHP)

• Large Website develop experience (e-Commerce / human-resource)

• Maintain site core APIs and core functions

• Develop new features based on business requests.

• DevOps: Introduce CI/CD to current workflow.

• Integrate UnitTest

• SaaS Experience: AWS, GCP

• Testing Experience: Test Campaign, Test Cases and Manual Testing

Technical Skills

Category	Name	Version	Year	Period
Programming Language	PHP	5.x / 7	2014 - now	over 5 years
Frameworks	Yii Framework (PHP)	1.1	2016-2019	over 2 years
Frameworks	Codelgniger (PHP)	2	2014-2016, 2019	over 3 years
Frameworks	Laravel		2014	
Databases	MySQL		2014,2016	
Tools (VCS)	Git		2014~now	
Tools (DevOps)	CircleCl		2019	
Tools (DevOps)	TravisCI		2017~2019	
Tools (DevOps)	CodeDeploy (AWS)		2017~2019	
Tools (DevOps)	Vagrant		2014~2019	
Tools (DevOps)	Docker		2019	
SaaS (AWS)	EC2, S3, Lambda, ApiGateway, ALB		2016~2019	
SaaS (GCP)	GCP		2019	

Language

- English (Fluent Speaking and Writing)
- Mandrin (Native)

Education

- · University of Pittsburgh, Pittsburgh, PA
- MS in Information Science, 2009~2010

Work Experience

Senior Backend Developer @ Zuvio - Taipei, Taiwan

2019/04

- Zuvio provides an app solution for college teachers/students
 where teachers can simply prepare class materials, do pop quiz and make roll calls.
 Also Zuvio provides a social network for college students.
- · Major Duty:
 - Develop and design new Api
 - Introduce CI tools (CircleCI) to improve code quality
 - Integrate PhpUnit to CircleCI to automate tests
 - Rapid develop new feature based on requests.
- · Project:
 - Test Monitoring system (Anti-cheat)
 - Using Websocket to monitor student class login behavior, create a dashboard for teachers to monitor.
 - User warning system (avoid user misbehave)
 - Automate current system task to alert users.

Web Developer @ 104 - Taipei, Taiwan

2016/07 - 2019/02

- 104 serves as largest human-resource website in Taiwan and considered as first choice when finding new jobs.
- Major Duty:
 - Maintain major website and develop new features, such as:
 - JobSearch Website (PC)
 - JobSearch Website (Mobile)
 - Common Api
 - Campaign websites
 - Develop campaign website with 100% cloud-based (AWS) infrastructure
 - Maintain and upgrade system
 - Https upgrade
 - Security updates
- · Projects:
 - Upgrade JobSearch feature
 - JobSearch Feature A/B Test
 - POC for new feature: JobSearch for Managers
 - Supersales: a campaign site with CI/CD integrated
 - AccountCenter Upgrade
 - Freshman: admin panel for PM
 - Heartfelt: a campaign site integrated with AWS Lambda (NodeJS)

Web Developer @ uitox - Taipei, Taiwan

2014/02 - 2016/04

- uitox is one of e-commerce innovators in Taiwan, providing one-stop e-commerce solutions for vendors.
- · Major Duty:
 - Maintain and enhance site-wise system core API: SaleQty API.
 - Maintain and enhance core pages: Item page.
 - Develop and extend in-house tools for PM and Developers.
- · Highlight Projects:
 - Crossborder: Integrate new data source and rules for oversea products.
 - Itempage Enhancement: Upgrade item page with new features.
 - Salegty API upgrade: Upgrade core SaleQTY API with new site features.
 - Flashsale: Integrate backend data to display discount items.
 - Custom Pages: Provide tools for PM/Vendor to create custom page.

Consultant @ SDLC Partners - Pittsburgh, PA, USA

2011/07 - 2012/11

- · Software Quality Assurance Analyst functions at Highmark QA team. (eMarketing Web Operations Team)
- · Functional Testing:
 - manual/automation function test including formulating test scenario and test cases, executing test cases and report, raising defect via Rational ClearQuest.
- · Parallel Testing:
 - parallel testing for both front-end and backend data warehouse system.

Quality Assurance / Developer @ Songwhale - Pittsburgh, PA, USA

2011/04 - 2011/07

- · Quality Assurance Engineer:
 - Formulate test strategies for various products: web app/mobile web/commercial website.
 - Develop and prioritize test scenarios in collaboration with business analyst and developer, execute test scripts
 manually or with automated tool.
 - Analyze defect level, detailed document bugs including screenshot/reproduce steps/possible root cause.
 - Utilize open source web UI test automation tool 'Selenium' with 'Bromine' integrated test tasking environment.
- · Web Developer:
 - Design website and database schema
 - Assist document MRD(Marketing Requirement Document)
 - · Develop mobile website utilizing MySQL and Php.

Side Projects

- M1GA 104 Hackathon
 - MobileWeb design
 - Dockerized

- SwingEventsTaipei (PHP/CD-enabled)
- PepeBot
 - NodeJS+AWALambda+ApiGateway+CD
 - Fun Chatbot
- WeddingHelper
 - NodeJS+AWALambda+ApiGateway+CD
- MouWorks
 - PersonalSite and Demo